{
  "response": [
    {
      "question": "Microservice could be considered as subset of __________",
      "option1": "Java",
      "option2": "SOA",
      "option3": "HTTP",
      "option4": "Cloud",
      "answer": "SOA"
    },
    {
      "question": "A monolithic application is _________",
      "option1": "built as single unit",
      "option2": "built to handle functionality and data of many application",
      "option3": "both of the above",
      "option4": "none of the above",
      "answer": "built as single unit"
    },
    {
      "question": "Single point failure examples is ___",
      "option1": "Monolithic",
      "option2": "Microservice",
      "option3": "both of the above",
      "option4": "None of the above",
      "answer": "Monolithic"
    },
    {
      "question": "Agile development and deployment is difficult in case of _________",
      "option1":  "Monolithic",
      "option2":  "Microservice",
      "option3":  "both of the above",
      "option4": "none of the above",
      "answer": "Monolithic"
    },
    {
      "question": "Software built as microservices can by definition be broken down into multiple component services. The statement is:",
      "option1":  "true",
      "option2": "false",
      "option3":"no idea",
      "option4":  "none",
      "answer": "true"
    },
    {
      "question": "Simple to develop test deploy scale represents __________",
      "option1":  "Monolithic",
      "option2":  "Microservice",
      "option3":  "both of the above",
      "option4": "none of the above",
      "answer": "Monolithic"
    },
    {
      "question": "In microservices the api gateway takes care of the security aspect by rendering",
      "option1": "Access token",
      "option2":"Key-value pair",
      "option3": "Encrypted keys",
      "option4":"Chassis keys",
      "answer": "Access token"
    },
    {
      "question": "Functional decomposition is an example of ____________",
      "option1":  "Monolithic",
      "option2":  "Microservice",
      "option3":  "both of the above",
      "option4": "none of the above",
      "answer": "Microservice"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which ensures to insulate the applications by acting as a barrier?",
      "option1": "API gateway",
      "option2":"Service Deployment",
      "option3": "Security control",
      "option4":"Microservices Chassis",
      "answer": "API gateway"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among these helps in developing a microservice quickly __________",
      "option1":  "Chassis",
      "option2":  "API Gateway",
      "option3":  "Service Registry",
      "option4": "Service Deployment",
      "answer":  "Chassis"
    },
    {
      "question": "Spring boot is example of _________",
      "option1":  "Service registry",
      "option2":  "Chassis framework",
      "option3":  "API Gateway",
      "option4": "Service Deployment",
      "answer":  "Chassis framework"
    },
    {
      "question": "Microservices based architecture enforces a modular structure.The above statement is:",
      "option1":  "true",
      "option2": "false",
      "option3":"no idea",
      "option4":  "none",
      "answer": "true"
    },
    {
      "question": "Queries in microservices architecture are implemented through _________",
      "option1":  "SQRS",
      "option2":  "CQRS",
      "option3":  "OQRS",
      "option4": "LQRS",
      "answer":  "CQRS"
    },
    {
      "question": "CQRS stands for in microservices _________",
     "option1":  "Command and Query Responsibility Segregation",
      "option2":  "Common Query Responsibility Segregation",
      "option3":  "Cleaner Query Responsibility Segregation",
      "option4": "Cipher Query Responsibility Segregation",
      "answer":  "Command and Query Responsibility Segregation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Microservices based architecture prefers __________",
     "option1":  "NoSql DBs",
      "option2":  "RDBMS DBs",
      "option3":  "MySql DBs",
      "option4": "No Dependency on any particular DBs",
      "answer":  "No Dependency on any particular DBs"
    },
    {
      "question": "External clients communicate with microservices using ____________",
     "option1":  "API Proxy",
      "option2":  "API Gateway",
      "option3":  "Service registry",
      "option4": "Security control",
      "answer":  "Service registry"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which acts as a database of services __________",
     "option1":  "API gateway",
      "option2":  "Microservice chassis",
      "option3":  "Service registry",
      "option4": "Security control",
      "answer":  "Service registry"
    }
  ]
}